Stop paying for expensive subscriptions like Hicksfield because I just built an MCP that allows
you to use every single creative model while only paying for what you use. The coolest part is
this MCP is completely free and you can run it with any AI models like Color, Chad Gbt and so much more.
So in this video I'm going to show you how I use it for my business and how you can do it too.
Now the problem with more subscription tools like Hicksfield is that sometimes you may only
want to use a creative model once but yet you still have to pay a subscription on a monthly basis.
With this MCP I'm able to connect directly to all of these different new creative models and
just pay for what I'm using. And by turning it into MCP it really makes it super simple because
you just have to connect it to your own AI tool like Color, Chad Gbt and you can generate any creative
materials directly from there. Just to give you an example I've used it to create every single asset
on my web page as well as my YouTube thumbnails or even the short form videos that I've been generating
right generating all of them through Color by using this one exact MCP. So to set this up is
extremely simple you can get this setup guide link in description below. And once you've
gained access to it you just have to follow along these steps to get it set up right away for you.
So let's go through this together. Firstly you just have to go down over here and you just have
to go into this web page called key AI. And so key AI is what this MCP is using as a connector
and a difference between key AI and other subscription platforms is that key AI is an aggregator that
allows us to connect directly to all of these different creative models and only pay for what we use.
Right so we don't have to pay a subscription to key AI we just have to top up the credits and
only pay for the model usage that we are using. So all you got to do is to create an account in key AI
okay and then you just have to add in some credits over here and then in key AI you can already
use this different models right you can click into one of this models here like nano banana two light
you can go into this and then you could just type in a prompt you could just generate it and you
can see the exact credit that you would take to use this exact model. We don't want to just be
creating all of these different creatives over here on this platform right the point of an MCP
is to be able to connect it to our own AI tools like cloud or chat GPT to generate assets for us
over there and that's where we go into step two which is to install the connector. So I've created
an MCP connector and all you got to do is to click into this and just download the MCP file here
clicking to this and then once you have that is super simple you just have to upload this into your
AI platform to set this up okay so I personally like to use cloud so I'm going to set this up
with cloud today but you can set this up with chat GPT as well okay so now that we're in cloud
let's set this up together all you got to do is to go into settings and click extensions okay
and then you just have to drag the MCP be filed over and you're ready to go. I'm going to drag it over
and paste this in and then you just click install and you'll have something like this and over here
in configure you would be requested to add in an API key right this is the API key that you will
get from key AI going to API keys create a new key and then give it a name and then you just have
to create that and then you just have to copy the API key and paste that back in over here okay once
that is done you're good to go you just have to set the permissions to always allow so that you can
let cloud use this exact model okay once this is set up right you can go into any new chat now
and you can click plus and make sure that the connector is set up so we have the key AI connector
here and once it's set up we can now just chat with cloud and make it generate any type of creative
materials for you you can use GPT image tool you can use cdans 2.0 and so much more let's say we
want to create an infographic around the six steps of AI automation with cloud code using the GPT
image tool model I just have to type that in click enter and now it's going to call the key AI
MCP and generate the full media for us okay and here we have a beautiful infographic about the
cloud code six step automation right and it uses the GPT image tool model and we don't have to pay
a subscription right we only pay per usage of this if I go back to key AI you can see my log and
this cost me about only 10 credits and it's not only for infographics right with an MCP connector
like this you can generate any types of creative media you could even create a UGC video right by
typing something like this create a UGC video of an O-man running and talking about life with
cdans 2.0 5 seconds clip and click enter and what cloud is going to do is it's going to call
key AI right now and generate this video for you okay and here we have it let's take a look
I'm 78 I still run every morning life don't wait for nobody so move
right super cool we're taking a step further if you want to make this even more impressive if
there's a certain method that you actually use to generate this different type of creative media
you can actually transform it into a custom skew that uses this MCP to allow cloud to generate
this different content for you as well to give you a simple example if you come back to the guide
I have a free skew that's called generate anything okay and what this free skew does is that
it helps you identify which models to use for the different tasks and it uses the MCP that I have
created to generate the creative models for you so let me show you how this actually works all
we got to do is to download this skew okay after you have downloaded the skew go back to cloud
and we can just upload the skew into cloud itself let's go into customize okay and you can add
in the skew so you can upload a skew and just upload the zip file that we have downloaded earlier
going to this and upload the zip file and you have the skew over here and make sure to turn this on
this is the instruction of how the skew work okay so now let's go into a new chat and with this new
skew it's now able to identify which model to use to generate what type of media let's
say I want to generate new audio and I do not know what to use right this model will actually go
into key AI and help me identify which model to use to generate audio for me let's say I want to
create a low five beat can you create a low five music beat for me and so as you can see over here
it's generating one directly for me right now because the skew I've set up allows it to actually
select the best model for the specific task and generate it directly for us if I go into key
AI over here you can see it's actually using soonal to generate the music for us right so it's
able to identify the specific model to use for our specific task and here we have it two low five
music that we can take a listen let's open this up
and you can try out this skew to generate different types of media for you and what this skew
would do is to identify the correct models for these specific tasks but really these just one simple
example right what really makes the skew even more valuable is how customized it can be for your
own specific task for example if you want to take it a step further and create a folder of
advert projects that you can create different types of advert for you you can use this same exact
mcp connector and connect it with a couple of skews like you can see over here I do have a couple
of skews that allows us to on board a new brand into this project generate new advert videos for us
I have a brand for this Oala Sunday tote bag and I'm able to use this mcp and the skews to generate
Adverts like this for us let's take a look this is a Valentine's gift
right and this is possible because I've created a skew that connects to this mcp inside this project
folder and now this project folder is sort of like my own advert agency that allows me to generate
different types of advert assets but besides just adverts this creative tools could also be used
for other use cases for example this is an example of a 3d web page kit that allows me to generate
3d web pages from this project itself so I've connected it to the mcp tool as well as give you a
couple of different custom skews allows cloth to use cdans 2.0 using this mcp to generate a media
that looks like this right so that I can use it for a final web page that looks like this take a
look right you can see this whole interactive animation experience is created because I've
connected it into a project that allows me to generate the visuals with cdans 2.0 and then
break it apart and then piece them all together and it's all possible because of this one mcp
connector it is also why I use to create graphic effects for my videos today check this out google
only just change video editing forever you cannot add any types of graphics into your video or change
your background or your clothes or even do this insane bottle trick that is crazy isn't it the
craziest part is I don't even have to do this all by myself my club buddies over here writes the
problem and do it all for me so in this video I want to show you how I did it and how you can do it
too so without further ado let's get right into it right all of this is generated using the other
model like google omni and gpt image to generate the different assets as well you can see how
versatile this is because this mcp allows me connect to all of these different models and create
different types of custom skews to generate different types of assets and projects for me so yeah
do give it a try and let me know what you would create with this specific tool itself if you
want to check out all the different guides and a lot of different AI projects and skews for your
own use cases like what I've shown earlier you can also check out all of them link in description
below or if you want to build custom systems like this you can reach out to us as well that being
said I hope you guys found this video useful if you like videos like this to give it a like and
subscribe and I'll see you guys in the next one peace